{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025970197","data":{"timestamp":" 947025970197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025975211","data":{"timestamp":" 947025975211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025983082","data":{"timestamp":" 947025983082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025995692","data":{"timestamp":" 947025995692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026011972","data":{"timestamp":" 947026011972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026019360","data":{"timestamp":" 947026019360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026027398","data":{"timestamp":" 947026027398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026035846","data":{"timestamp":" 947026035846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026051030","data":{"timestamp":" 947026051030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026059107","data":{"timestamp":" 947026059107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026069177","data":{"timestamp":" 947026069177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026082838","data":{"timestamp":" 947026082838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026090898","data":{"timestamp":" 947026090898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026099365","data":{"timestamp":" 947026099365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026107944","data":{"timestamp":" 947026107944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026121287","data":{"timestamp":" 947026121287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026130623","data":{"timestamp":" 947026130622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026139171","data":{"timestamp":" 947026139171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026146393","data":{"timestamp":" 947026146393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026155477","data":{"timestamp":" 947026155477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026167373","data":{"timestamp":" 947026167373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026174362","data":{"timestamp":" 947026174362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026181579","data":{"timestamp":" 947026181579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026189021","data":{"timestamp":" 947026189021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026194953","data":{"timestamp":" 947026194953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026207685","data":{"timestamp":" 947026207685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026216528","data":{"timestamp":" 947026216528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026225044","data":{"timestamp":" 947026225043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026232524","data":{"timestamp":" 947026232524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026238342","data":{"timestamp":" 947026238341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026247314","data":{"timestamp":" 947026247314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026260266","data":{"timestamp":" 947026260266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026267293","data":{"timestamp":" 947026267293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026279617","data":{"timestamp":" 947026279617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026284390","data":{"timestamp":" 947026284390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026304416","data":{"timestamp":" 947026304415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026315522","data":{"timestamp":" 947026315521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_014538"," gameId":" b92bb780-4a51-4b38-a792-db02738857f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}